發言。
立法會主席。
多謝主席。
石禮謙議員就香港特別行政區廉政。
二零一六年報向本會發言石大軒言。
The ICAC has been fighting corruption with a holistic approach.
通過有效法律執法、預防和教育。
In my capacity as a member of the advisory committee on corruption, I hereby brief members.
Through the subterfuge, the public abhors corruption and will not want to be corrupt.
它 enhances system and rules to eliminate corruption loopholes, so that the greedy cannot be corrupt.
On the Independent Commission Against Corruption (ICAC) annual report 2016, tabled in the Council today.
它也擴及到社區， endeavering to change the public's attitude from meek tolerance to rejection.
它 discharge its enforcement duties impartially, making corruption a high-risk crime, and the unscrupulous dare not be corrupt.
由私營部門佔29%，與政府部門有關，及8%涉及公營機構，一個模式，已維持數年。
Despite a slight increase of 3% in corruption complaints compared to 2015, the ICAC annual survey 2016 conducted by an independent research institute indicated no sign of deterioration.
About election malpractices and illegal activities.
which is 0.1% lower than the previous year.
The public stay vigilant and intolerant against corruption.
According to the annual survey, only 1.2%.
Of the respondents, have come across corruption in the past twelve months.
和選前 briefing， to appeal to candidates and electors to abide by the law.
腐敗預防摺疊、training videos and toolkits on building management were published.
2016 was an election year in Hong Kong, and the ICAC received a total of 858 complaints.
To uphold clean and fair elections, the ICAC have been taking vigorous law enforcement actions against corrupt practices.
Using a zero to ten rating scale, of which zero represents total rejection, and ten total tolerance of corruption.
Noting that the corruption facilitated tender rigging activities remain a concern for the public, the ICA took a robust enforcement action against such activities.
Combined with efforts to provide corruption prevention advice on the building rehabilitation facilitating services, the pilot scheme launched by the URA, besides
The mean score of tolerance to corruption was 0.7, 0.7， and the public also indicated support for the ICAC's anti-corruption work.
and updated to deliver anti-corruption messages to owners, owners, corporations and relevant parties and organisations involved in building management and maintenance.
During the year, ICAC received 16 complaints concerning corruption facilitated tender rigging activities, which account for a small percentage of total number of complaints.
在二零一六，的腐敗情況在香港，仍穩定和受控。ICAC收到兩千八百九十一個非選舉相關的腐敗舉報，其中百分之六十三被針對。
In collaboration with the relevant government departments, the ICAC have been reviewing the electoral legislation and procedures to ensure a sound and reliable voter registration system, and to disseminate anti-vote rigging messages through extensive publicity.
到下一個世代。
And this is indeed a hard-earned achievement.
and pass the torch of value of probability.
The success of the battle against corruption is hard-earned.
《 integrity and corruption prevention guide on managing relationship with public servants》。
to stay abreast of the latest social development and areas of public concern.
主席和 fellow members，今天香港是國際上聞名，為一間最清潔的城市。
自2016，ICAC開始推出一「territory-wide」，或「for integrity education and publicity」，計劃。
三年道德促進計劃，為上市公司協助管理私人組織在提升企業管治。
But let us forget that in the 1960s and the 70s, bribery have been part of the people's daily lives. The success.
69 assignment reports on the system and procedures of government departments, public bodies and non-government organisations were completed.
By reaching out to different strata of the community through an array of activities, including a slogan and icon design competition, the ICAC investigators 2016 television drama series.
一眾range of best practices checklists were published during the year, namely sample code of conduct for managers and staff of kindergartens, corruption prevention guide on administration of public-private partnership programme for healthcare services.
Advice were provided to public and private organisations on nearly 1,500 occasions to strengthen their internal control. The ICAE also offer various integrity training programmes to senior civil servants and launch a tree.
參與在香港書展和地區活動，與18個區議會合辦的活動，提高他們對正義重要性的認識，鞏固公眾對反貪工作的支持。
And is attributed to the rule of law, a sound legal and independent judicial foundation, a virtues and relentless anti-corruption regime, as well as professional graft fighters, an intolerance of corruption and support for ICAC anti-corruption work.
by the public.
主席，我所以 submit。
林建峯議員就廉政公署事宜投訴委員。
Let us continue to render our full support for the work of ICAC.
On behalf of the commissioner of ICAC, I wish to express my sincere gratitude to all of them.
equally important are the invaluable contributions of members of the ICAC advisory committees and this council.
Fight corruption with three-pronged approach on the fronts of investigation, prevention and education to keep Hong Kong fair, just, stable and prosperous.
作為成員會委員會委員，我理解ICAC會承認高期望，即係社會對佢嘅工作。佢會一直繼續履行佢嘅法定責任，維護公正原則。